My name is Ramsey Hammed Odhiambo.
My problem is avascular necrosis of the hip.
I have been using these crutches for four years.
I can't play with my friends at school.
I want to walk by myself.
Please, Man of God, help my son.
What happened to your child?
He has avascular necrosis of the hip.
How are you? What's your name?
Ramsey Hammed Odhiambo.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Little boy, this is your mum?
Yes.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Healing In Jesus' Name
Who is Jesus?
Jesus is the Son of God.
Healing In Jesus' Name
Healed In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus!
Thank You, Jesus, my son is healed!
Healed In Jesus' Name
TESTIMONY TIME
My name is Christine Zennah Kierai.
The boy beside me is my son, Ramsey.
The baby here is my baby girl.
We are from Kenya.
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN was the illness of my son.
He had been suffering for four years with an incurable disease.
He had difficulty in breathing, chest pain, back pain and the disease even affected the hip.
So, he used to support himself, using crutches.
He couldn't play with his friends at school.
He used to skip school; he would normally go to school twice a week.
I knew that by coming here, he would receive his healing and deliverance.
When we were in Kenya, we went to several hospitals but all was in vain.
The last time I was in the hospital, he was given painkillers and was also booked for an operation.
Most of the time, I was the one supporting him.
For how long had he been using the crutches?
For four years.
It had affected him mentally and spiritually
and even in his education, he wasn't performing well.
When I saw the man of God approaching us, I was shocked and started shivering.
Then, the man of God laid his hands on my son, meditating and praying.
Instantly, my son stood up and started walking!
Master Ramsey Odhiambo & Mother
Healing Testimony
In fact, the pain he was feeling on his chest and back, disappeared immediately.
He can now walk without crutches, bathe, eat and do everything by himself.
So you don't need to help him anymore?
Yes.
Shall we put our hands together for our Lord Jesus!
Testimony Time
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Ramsey Hammed Odhiambo.
I am 9 years old.
I am from Kenya.
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN was avascular necrosis disease,
which affected my hip bone.
I couldn't walk by myself; I used crutches.
I couldn't play with my friends at school or at home.
My mum used to lock me inside so that I could rest.
Last week on Sunday, the man of God laid hands on me
and I suddenly felt something moving in my body.
I received my healing immediately!
Healed Of Avascular Necrosis Of The Hip
No Longer Using Crutches
Wow.
Healed Of Avascular Necrosis Of The Hip
No Longer Using Crutches
And today, to the glory of God, Ramsey can walk.
Can you walk in the midst of the children of God to see how you are doing today.
Healed Of Avascular Necrosis Of The Hip
No Longer Using Crutches
Yes, we can see the little brother walking for the first time in four years.
Since the man of God prayed for him, the Lord has transformed him.
Today, he is standing to the glory of God to share his wonderful testimony
of how God Almighty has wiped away the tears of the family.
Believe in God and He will fulfill your dream.
Amen!
Just as the Lord has done in the life of this little brother,
He will do it for you, in Jesus' name.
You should have faith and wait upon the Lord because with God, everything is possible.
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
My name is Christine Zennah Kierai.
The boy beside me is my son Ramsey Hammed Odhiambo.
We are from Kenya.
I would like to say thank you for healing my son.
I can afford to smile today because my son is walking.
I have been enduring a lot of pain in the past but now, my past is over.
Apart from that, I would like to say thank you again to the man of God
because after healing my son, we were given accommodation free of charge,
everything was taken care of.
May God bless him abundantly, in Jesus' name.
Amen. We thank you for receiving the help from The SCOAN family.
We are very happy to see him healthy and happy today after what God has done in his life.
The blessings of God are unlimited.
That is why before you go, we also want to give this gift to you.
This is a cash gift of 1,500 USD.
Prophet T.B. Joshua is actually giving you this as a scholarship for your son,
for you to take back with you to Kenya.
I want to thank the man of God.
May God continue blessing him abundantly.
What he has done for us - nobody has ever considered us.
May God bless him for me.
Ramsey, we would like to hear some words from you.
My name is Ramsey Hammed Odhiambo.
I'm from Kenya.
I am nine years old.
I thank God for healing me and T.B. Joshua for giving me a scholarship.
So now that you have been given thise scholarship for your school,
how are you going to do at school now?
I will improve; I will give my best and come out with good grades.
Amen. God is the Rewarder of our efforts
and we know that definitely, as you give that effort,
God is ready to give back to you abundantly, in Jesus' name.
Amen!
Thank You, Jesus!
TT: Mel Flowers 20/04/2019